{
    "warmup": [
        {
            "id": "w-2-0",
            "question": "register muddy",
            "options": [
                "register-muscle",
                "register-moral",
                "register-muddy",
                "resident-model"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "register-muddy"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-3-0",
            "question": "messy throat",
            "options": [
                "messyThroat",
                "messyThanks",
                "messyThought",
                "messageTender"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "messyThroat"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-1-0",
            "question": "gear distance",
            "options": [
                "gearDistinct",
                "gameDiscount",
                "gearDistance",
                "gearDistrict"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "gearDistance"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-5-0",
            "question": "stomach group",
            "options": [
                "stomach group",
                "stomach grand",
                "station grand",
                "stomach grave"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "stomach group"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-0-0",
            "question": "runny trash",
            "options": [
                "runny-trash",
                "ruddy-tower",
                "runny-trick",
                "runny-truck"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "runny-trash"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-4-0",
            "question": "country creative",
            "options": [
                "countryComplete",
                "countryCreative",
                "countyCrushing",
                "countryComposed"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "countryCreative"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "3-0",
            "question": "narrow actor",
            "options": [
                "narrow-adept",
                "narrow-ample",
                "narrow-actor",
                "nobody-alert"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "narrow-actor"
        },
        {
            "id": "2-0",
            "question": "dual black",
            "options": [
                "dual-block",
                "dual-blank",
                "drop-blind",
                "dual-black"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "dual-black"
        },
        {
            "id": "9-2",
            "question": "precious capital",
            "options": [
                "precious consist",
                "property cancer",
                "precious careful",
                "precious capital"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "precious capital"
        },
        {
            "id": "4-0",
            "question": "creepy honey",
            "options": [
                "creepy-honey",
                "creepy-hefty",
                "creepy-hope",
                "cookie-homely"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "creepy-honey"
        },
        {
            "id": "5-0",
            "question": "wake sympathy",
            "options": [
                "wake-strength",
                "wake-sympathy",
                "will-striking",
                "wake-shameful"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "wake-sympathy"
        },
        {
            "id": "4-1",
            "question": "creepy honey",
            "options": [
                "creepyHoney",
                "collarHefty",
                "creepyHook",
                "creepyHost"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "creepyHoney"
        },
        {
            "id": "2-1",
            "question": "dual black",
            "options": [
                "dualBlank",
                "dualBrick",
                "deadBread",
                "dualBlack"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "dualBlack"
        },
        {
            "id": "0-2",
            "question": "league county",
            "options": [
                "league coffee",
                "league county",
                "league common",
                "lesson costly"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "league county"
        },
        {
            "id": "4-2",
            "question": "creepy honey",
            "options": [
                "creepy honey",
                "creepy hollow",
                "creepy hotel",
                "credit hefty"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "creepy honey"
        },
        {
            "id": "0-0",
            "question": "league county",
            "options": [
                "league-courage",
                "league-county",
                "letter-collar",
                "league-cookie"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "league-county"
        },
        {
            "id": "1-2",
            "question": "feline notable",
            "options": [
                "feline notable",
                "feline nonstop",
                "factor note",
                "feline noxious"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "feline notable"
        },
        {
            "id": "7-0",
            "question": "snappy ability",
            "options": [
                "spirit-amazing",
                "snappy-ability",
                "snappy-admired",
                "snappy-alarmed"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "snappy-ability"
        },
        {
            "id": "8-1",
            "question": "double valuable",
            "options": [
                "doubleValuable",
                "doubleVigorous",
                "doubleVengeful",
                "drawerValue"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "doubleValuable"
        },
        {
            "id": "5-1",
            "question": "wake sympathy",
            "options": [
                "wakeSurround",
                "wakeSympathy",
                "westSpecific",
                "wakeStriking"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "wakeSympathy"
        },
        {
            "id": "1-0",
            "question": "feline notable",
            "options": [
                "feline-notable",
                "filthy-natural",
                "feline-normal",
                "feline-normal"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "feline-notable"
        },
        {
            "id": "6-1",
            "question": "mail tomorrow",
            "options": [
                "mailTempting",
                "messTourist",
                "mailTomorrow",
                "mailTattered"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "mailTomorrow"
        },
        {
            "id": "5-2",
            "question": "wake sympathy",
            "options": [
                "wake swimming",
                "wake sympathy",
                "wife shameful",
                "wake studious"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "wake sympathy"
        },
        {
            "id": "2-2",
            "question": "dual black",
            "options": [
                "dual bleak",
                "dark blind",
                "dual blank",
                "dual black"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "dual black"
        },
        {
            "id": "7-1",
            "question": "snappy ability",
            "options": [
                "snappyAttempt",
                "snappyAbility",
                "sinfulAlarmed",
                "snappyAwesome"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "snappyAbility"
        },
        {
            "id": "7-2",
            "question": "snappy ability",
            "options": [
                "snappy awesome",
                "snappy ability",
                "stroke absolute",
                "snappy abroad"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "snappy ability"
        },
        {
            "id": "6-2",
            "question": "mail tomorrow",
            "options": [
                "mail trifling",
                "mail tangible",
                "mail tomorrow",
                "mark tourist"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "mail tomorrow"
        },
        {
            "id": "8-2",
            "question": "double valuable",
            "options": [
                "double valuable",
                "doting velvety",
                "double variety",
                "double vigorous"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "double valuable"
        },
        {
            "id": "3-1",
            "question": "narrow actor",
            "options": [
                "narrowAlarm",
                "narrowAlive",
                "narrowActor",
                "naiveAngry"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "narrowActor"
        },
        {
            "id": "9-1",
            "question": "precious capital",
            "options": [
                "preciousCompany",
                "presenceClassic",
                "preciousContext",
                "preciousCapital"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "preciousCapital"
        },
        {
            "id": "1-1",
            "question": "feline notable",
            "options": [
                "felineNotable",
                "felineNotice",
                "famousNoted",
                "felineNonstop"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "felineNotable"
        },
        {
            "id": "3-2",
            "question": "narrow actor",
            "options": [
                "narrow agent",
                "naive apple",
                "narrow actor",
                "narrow adult"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "narrow actor"
        },
        {
            "id": "9-0",
            "question": "precious capital",
            "options": [
                "previous-context",
                "precious-classic",
                "precious-cancer",
                "precious-capital"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "precious-capital"
        },
        {
            "id": "6-0",
            "question": "mail tomorrow",
            "options": [
                "mail-tangible",
                "mail-tattered",
                "mail-tomorrow",
                "mall-tempting"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "mail-tomorrow"
        },
        {
            "id": "8-0",
            "question": "double valuable",
            "options": [
                "double-valuable",
                "double-violent",
                "dreary-variable",
                "double-velvety"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "double-valuable"
        },
        {
            "id": "0-1",
            "question": "league county",
            "options": [
                "leadingCourage",
                "leagueCounty",
                "leagueCostly",
                "leagueCourse"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "leagueCounty"
        }
    ]
}